Guide to the McMurry Richey papers, 1935-1985 UA.29.02.0227
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
McMurry Richey papers
1935-1985
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Richey, McMurry Smith
UA.29.02.0227
15 Linear Feet
Dr. McMurry Richey was a faculty member of the Duke Divinity School and long-time director of the school's continuing education program. His papers cover a variety of topics, including materials related to continuing education, Duke Divinity School's annual convocation, the church and society, ethics, race relations, Duke's integration, and poverty.
Provenance
The McMurry Richey papers were received by the University Archives as a transfer in January, 1986.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Collection Overview
This collection is divided into nine series, each representing a different aspect of Dr. Richey's work.
The Convocation and Pastor's School papers series covers the planning, publicity, correspondence, speaker invitations, and other aspects of the annual convocation held at Duke.
The Continuing Education series covers Richey's work as director of continuing education for the Divinity School and includes research and publications on continuing education, lecture notes, workshop materials, materials concerning other continuing education programs, correspondence, and memoranda.
The Curriculum Committee series has materials related to the Divinity School curriculum and the revision process it underwent during Richey's time at Duke.
The Junior Seminars series covers the syllabi and lesson plans for various sections of Junior seminars.
Reports, Research and Correspondence covers Richey's research into a variety of topics, including the church, race, poverty, the ministry, and lectureships as well as correspondence with professional colleagues and ministers on the same.
Early Course Materials and Student Work consists of Richey's graduate work, notes, and (ungraded) copies of work completed by Richey's students. Also included are materials related to race relations, integration of Duke University, reactionary exteremism, and social reform.
Ethics contains notes on different ethical systems and were likely used as lesson outlines for teaching.
Laity and Related Topics is an accumulation of publications and correspondence surrounding the interaction of lay people with theology and the ministry.
Church and Society Programs contains materials examining the links between the church, ethical sytems, business, poverty, and race.
Historical note
After graduation from the Duke Divinity School, McMurry "Mac" Richey entered the Western North Carolina Conference of the Methodist Episcopal Church, South. Ordained elder in 1943, he served pastorates until 1947 (Central Methodist, Asheville; Cullowhee; Kerr Street, Concord; and Brevard Street, Charlotte). Throughout his career, Richey took strong stands on social, political and economic issues. He made prophetic and sometimes unpopular witness on race, war and labor. For instance, speaking out for workers' interests and rights to organize in mill-owned Concord earned him a short appointment and a premature relocation.
He then moved to the University of Houston where he served as director of Methodist Student Work, director of religious activities and instructor in philosophy and religion before returning to Duke for a Ph.D. in religion.
After completion of his doctorate, Richey taught theology, Wesley studies, and religious education at Duke Divinity School. From 1972 on, he served as director of continuing education, and for nearly 15 years organized, promoted and led student and pastor study-seminars to Mexico. Conversations between the Mexican and U.S. church and the interpretation of Latin American Christianity became a centerpiece of Richey's life and work. He retired in 1983.
Biographical information taken from http://divinity.duke.edu/publications/2006.01/depts/deaths.htm
Continuing education -- United States; Southern States -- Race relations; Durham (N.C.) -- Race relations; Theology -- Study and teaching; Duke University. Divinity School; Richey, McMurry Smith
- Convocation and Pastors' School Papers, 1952-1983; 1
  - Convocation Brochures 1958 to 1979 (except 1960, 1977), 1958-1979 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Plans, 1983 June-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation Vitae Pictures, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Convocation Plans, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - Board of Managers, Convocation Plans, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Brochure Materials, Correspondence, 1978 March-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Convocation Speakers, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Convocation Worship, 1972-1977 (Box 1)
  - Convocation Brochure and Data on Speakers, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1975-1976 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1976 July-September (Box 1)
  - Convocation, 1976 September-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Speakers, 1976 July-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Mini-Courses, Music, Worship, 1976 July-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Brochure, Publicity, Schedule, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Board of Managers, Convocation Plans, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
  - Convocation, 1972-1974; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Inquiries, Enrollments, Mini-Course Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Convocation, 1973 March-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Brochure, Publicity, 1973 March-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1971-1973 (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Follow-Up, Plans, 1973-1974 (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Remaining Preparations and Follow-Up Letters, 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Divinity School Gray Lectures, Plans, 1970-1972 (Box 1)
  - Board of Managers, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
  - Frank S. Hickman Lectureship, 1971 March-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - Board of Managers, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Brochure and Publicity Materials, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Speakers, Letters, Data, Schedules, 1971-1972 (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Speakers, Letters, Information, 1971 March-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Worship, 1971 September-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Follow-Up, Letters, Records, Minutes, Notes, 1971 August-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Correspondence with Speakers, Leaders, 1970 May-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Worship, 1970, October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Brochure, Publicity, Biographical Data, 1970 July-October (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Mailing Lists, 1964-1970 (Box 1)
  - Hickman Lectureship, Dr. Richard W. Cain, 1970 October-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation and Pastors' School: Letters of Invitation to Speakers and Leaders, 1969 January-November (Box 1)
  - Convocation: Misc. Correspondence, 1969 August-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Publicity, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1969 April-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Speakers, Brochure, Publicity, Data, 1968 June-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1965-1968 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Finances, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
  - Board of Managers of the North Carolina Conference, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Program Outline and Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Board of Managers, NC Pastors' School, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
  - Board of Managers, NC Pastors' School, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1966-1967 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Gray Lecturer, 1966 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Follow-Up, 1966 November (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Materials to Sort and File, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Speakers, Publicity, Brochure, 1965-1966 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Program, Brochure, 1965 August-November (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Miscellaneous, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Speakers, Pictures, Topics, Biographies, 1963-1965 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Board of Managers Executive Committee, 1965 July-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Speakers, Leaders, Schedules, Arrangements, 1965 September-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Follow-Up, 1965 November (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Executive Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Brochure and Publicity Materials, 1964 August-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Program and Publicity, 1963-1964 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1963 October-November (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Follow-Up, 1964-1965 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Services of Worship, 1964 October (Box 2)
  - North Carolina Pastors' School, 1964-1967 (Box 2)
  - North Carolina Pastors' School, 1961-1964 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, Board of Managers, and Committees, 1963 January-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Speakers, 1963 January-October (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, Brochure, and Programs, 1962 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1962 September-November (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1961-1962 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Convocation, 1960-1961; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Brochure, Plans for Program, 1961 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Plans, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Board of Managers, President, Executive, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Lecturers, Topics, Publicity Material, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Alumni Reunion, Dinner, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - Convocation: Miscellaneous, 1960 October-November (Box 3)
  - Convocation: Program, Outline, Bulletins, Participants, Dinners, 1959-1960 (Box 3)
  - Convocation: Promotion, District Superintendents, District Representatives, Mailing Lists, 1960 June-September (Box 3)
  - Pastors' School, 1952-1957 (Box 3)
  - Pastors' School, 1956-1963 (Box 3)
- Continuing Education, 1960-1985; 2
  - Continuing Education, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Perkins School of Theology, 1966-1972 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Other Fields and Professions, 1972 (Box 3)
  - Connolly Gamble and Union's Continuing Education, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Union New York, John H. Hendrickson, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Princeton, Jack Cooper, 1972 (Box 3)
  - SACEM and Continuing Education in other Situations, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - Pastoral Psychology Book Club, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Sample Brochures, Programs from SACEM, 1971-1972; 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Center for Continuing Education, Candler School of Theology, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Publicity Samples, 1971-1975 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Sample Letters, Announcements, 1972 (Box 3)
  - North Carolina Commission on Continuing Education for Ministry, 1970-1973 (Box 3)
  - For Continuing Education Committee, 1972 August-October (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminars: Applications, 1972 August-September (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminars, 1972 September (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminar: Romans, Dr. Moody Smith Jr., 1972 August-October (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Study: Dr. Olivia P. Stokes, 1972 March-October (Box 3)
  - JSAC Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Salvation Today Seminar, 1972 October-December (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminar: India, Dr. Creighton Lacy, 1972 August-September (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Reading Program: Harmon L. Smith, "Christian Ethics and Modern Medicine", 1972 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Theological Education In-Residence Reading Program, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - Wilfred Bailey Visit, 1972 September (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education: Church, Management, Finances, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - M. Novak, WNC Seminar, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education Consultation: NC WNC, 1974 June-October (Box 3)
  - Doctrine and Doctrinal Standards, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Family Financial Planning: Clergymen as Financial Advisors, Dr. K. Edwin Graham, 1973 (Box 3)
  - Seminar: Black Church Strategies, 1973 January-April (Box 3)
  - Ministerial Career Review: Stages, Crises, Resources, 1973 June-October (Box 3)
  - Parish Planning and Operation Seminars, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Greensboro District Seminar: Dr. Robb L. Wilson, "The Church and Social Change", 1973 June-October (Box 3)
  - Seminar: "The Church and the Spirit", 1973 September-November (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Reading Program: Rosters of Participants, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
  - In-Residence Seminars: Plans, Suggestions, 1973 March-July (Box 4)
  - Plans for Extension Studies: Charlotte, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - WNC Seminar: Roll, Credit, Aid, Assignments, etc., 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - The Church and the New Evangelicalism, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Clergy and Laity Seminar, 1973 February-June (Box 4)
  - WNC Preaching Seminar: Lake Junaluska, 1973 August-October (Box 4)
  - Young Pastors' Seminar, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Personal Growth Laboratory, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - UMTS Continuing Education Directors, Cincinnati, 1974 January-March (Box 4)
  - Communications Workshop, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Parish Development Consultation for WNC, 1973 (Box 4)
  - SACEM, 1974 March-July (Box 4)
  - Tri-District Brevard Continuing Education Project, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - "Motivation for Continuing Education" by Mark Rouch, 1974 March (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education Report and Catalogue Copy, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education Planning, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - SACEM Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Carlyle Marney and Interpreters' House, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education: Plans, 1963-1971 (Box 4)
  - American Academy of Religion, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Evangelism Consultation, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Summer Institute: Inquiries, Applications, Letters, 1974 June-July (Box 4)
  - Conference of Charismatic Movements: Publicity, Applications, and Registrations, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Grailville Consultation: Seminary Continuing Education Personnel, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: Virginia, 1970-1973 (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: South Carolina, 1974 (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: South Carolina Miscellaneous Materials (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: South Carolina, 1971-1972 (Box 4)
  - South Carolina Plans: Working with Lutheran Theological Southern Seminary, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: South Carolina, 1973 April-November (Box 4)
  - Divinity School Seminars: Virginia, 1973 February-November (Box 4)
  - Contemporary Theology, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
  - Interfaith Council for Family Financial Planning: Annual Meeting, 1974 April-October (Box 4)
  - "How do we do Theology in the South Today?", 1974 February-April (Box 4)
  - Consultation: The Family and Changing Values, 1974 September-November (Box 4)
  - Young Pastors' Seminar, 1974 March-November (Box 4)
  - South Carolina Pastors' School Plans, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
  - Brevard Seminar, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Seminar: The Psalms and the Spiritual Life, 1977 July-November (Box 5)
  - Seminar: Pre-Retirement Planning, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Seminar: Education and Evangelism Workshop, 1976 September-November (Box 5)
  - Salisbury District Study Group, 1977 July-October (Box 5)
  - Consultation: Small Membership Churches, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Personal Growth Laboratory for Black Church Leaders, 1975 April (Box 5)
  - Spiritual Life Retreat and Other Worship Services, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Plans, Transition, 1973-1975 (Box 5)
  - Advent-Christmas Sermon Workshop, 1976 October-November (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Plans, 1976 May-July (Box 5)
  - Center for Continuing Education: Appalachian State University, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: R. Bruce Pate Directed Study, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Seminar at Interpreter's House and International Growth Center: "Management for Ministry", 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Duke Endowment Scholarships, 1978 April-May (Box 5)
  - Dumont Clarke Scholarships, 1975 May (Box 5)
  - Requisition Forms for Continuing Education, Honoraria Expenses Scholarships, Undated (Box 5)
  - AJS Conference: "Ancient Hebrew Prayer", 1974 February-March (Box 5)
  - Liturgy and Education Materials, 1977 March-June (Box 5)
  - Liturgy and Education Correspondence, 1977 January-June (Box 5)
  - Originals, 1973-1977 (Box 5)
  - Seminar: Lenten Preaching, 1977-1978 (Box 5)
  - Summer Campus Institute for Ministry, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education Plans, 1976 July-November (Box 5)
  - Dr. Stuart C. Henry, 1969-1971 (Box 5)
  - Parish Ministry Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education, 1973-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: "Nation Under God", 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Liturgy and Education, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Institutes, 1976 January-May (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Past Events, 1975 April-December (Box 5)
  - Brevard, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Finances, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Director, 1975 September-November (Box 5)
  - Dialogue, Ethics, Shriver, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Continuing Education: Future Events, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - "Preaching and Worship in Churches of Small Membership", 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - WNC Extension Studies Seminar, 1975 April-May (Box 5)
  - Summer Institute: Church Education, 1975 January-July (Box 5)
  - Seminar: Ferrum College, Virginia, 1975 July-August (Box 5)
  - Dean John Wilkinson, St. George's College, Jerusalem, 1974 January-May (Box 5)
  - Summer Institute Promotion, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Consultation on Charismatic Movements Planning, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - Theology for Black Churchmen, 1974 January-April (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Extension Courses, NC, WNC, 1972 April (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Materials, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Faculty Offerings, 1969-1973 (Box 6)
  - "Family Dynamics and Financial Planning", 1975 June-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Plans, Leaders, Courses, Publicity, 1975 January-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Clinics: Plans, 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Dean Edward H. Patey, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Applications, Registrations, Scholarships, 1975 May-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Clinics: Duke Divinity School, 1971-1973 (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Applications, 1973 April-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Plans, Brochures, Publicity, 1973 April-June (Box 6)
  - Summer Clinic in Theology, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Summer Clinics, 1971-1972 (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Correspondence and Mailings, 1971-1976 (Box 6)
  - Spring Institute for Ministry, 1977-1978 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Greensboro Events, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Campus Ministry Institute, 1976 June-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry: Leaders, Letters, Courses, Program, 1974 February-July (Box 6)
  - Summer Institute for Ministry, 1974 (Box 6)
  - "The Pastor and the Charismatics", 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Seminar: Virginia, 1973-1974 (Box 6)
  - Workshop on Preaching: Fort Bragg, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - WNC Extension Studies: Dr. Lycurgus Starken, "The Holy Spirit", 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Plans, Schedules, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - State Commission on Continuing Education, 1973-1975 (Box 6)
  - North Carolina Conference: Continuing Education Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - WNC Conference Committee on Continuing Education, 1972-1974 (Box 6)
  - Sermon Workshop for Summer Preaching, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Virginia Conference, Pastors' Convocation, 1971-1977 (Box 6)
  - "Ministry to the Formerly Married", 1977 August-October (Box 6)
  - Advent and Christmas Sermon Workshop, 1977 October (Box 6)
  - Seminar: Campus Ministry, 1976-1977 (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: OKI, 1975-1976 (Box 6)
  - Young Pastors' Seminar, 1974-1977 (Box 6)
  - Workshop: Albemarle District, Pfeiffer College, "Biblical Preaching Today", 1976 (Box 6)
  - Seminar: Black Church Studies, "Decision-Making in the Black Church", 1976 October (Box 6)
  - Koehler, 1977 February-March (Box 6)
  - Dr. Jose Miguez Bonino: Schedule, Invitations, Announcements, Correspondence, 1977 February-March (Box 6)
  - Continuing Education: Inquiries, Mailing Addresses, 1972-1976 (Box 6)
  - Lay-Clergy Dialogue: Lake Junaluska, 1973-1975 (Box 7)
  - Parish Ministry Fund, 1982-1985 (Box 7)
  - PMF Scholarship Grants/Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Parish Ministry Fund, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
  - Parish Ministry Fund, 1978 February (Box 7)
  - Parish Ministry Fund, 1968-1979 (Box 7)
  - Institute for Homiletical Studies, 1965-1972 (Box 7)
  - Book Recommendation for WNC Institute, Homiletical, 1972 April-May (Box 7)
  - Methodist-Catholic Dialogues: Charlotte, 1974 February (Box 7)
  - M. Wilson Nesbitt, Duke Endowment, 1974-1978 (Box 7)
  - Laymen's Consultations on the Church, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: Virginia, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: Virginia, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: South Carolina, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: South Carolina, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: South Carolina, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminar: North Carolina, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminars: South Carolina Conference, 1960-1967 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminars: Follow-Up Letters to Leaders and Speakers, 1969 April-May (Box 7)
  - Divinity School Seminars: North Carolina, Western N.C., Letters to Leaders and Speakers, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - Seminars, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
  - Duke Divinity School Seminars: Follow-Up Letters, 1968 November-December (Box 7)
  - Seminars: Finances, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Seminars: Richmond, Virginia, 1967 October-November (Box 7)
  - Seminars, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Seminars: Correspondence, Hosts, 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Seminars, 1967-1969 (Box 7)
  - Seminars, 1962-1966 (Box 7)
  - Divinity School Plans for Continued Education, 1966-1970 (Box 7)
  - Divinity School Plans for Continued Education, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Continuing Education Consultation, 1969 February-May (Box 7)
  - Working Paper on Study Guides for Continuing Education, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Continuing Theological Education: Nashville Seminar Materials, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Theological and Continuing Education, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, 1969 May; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Contemporary Society and Education Extension, 1968 November (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, 1967-1969 (Box 8)
  - Photos Convocation Speakers, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Council on Aging and Human Development: Committee on Continuing Education, 1983 October (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education Plans, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - NC Conference Committee: Two Career Families in Ministry, circa 1984 (Box 8)
  - Statesville District Seminar, 1984 March (Box 8)
  - WNC Probationers, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - District Seminars and Workshops, 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - J. H. Westerhoff's Continuing Education 105: Education as a Pastoral Ministry, 1977 July (Box 8)
  - Seminar with West German Ministers, 1980-1982 (Box 8)
  - Continuing Education, 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Supervision Workshop, 1983 April-May (Box 8)
  - Mark Rouch, International Growth Center, 1979 January-August (Box 8)
  - NC Continuing Education Committee/Board of Ministry, 1974-1979 (Box 8)
  - WNC Continuing Education Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 8)